翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
There are two more topics that we'll need to cover in our Java crash course today before you can really get started on project zero.
在项目0前，今天的 Java 速成课还有两个内容
The first is, let's talk a little bit more
第一个是，我想再多说两句
about public static void main string braces args
关于 public static void main(String[] args)
and get a sense of what this all means.
真正理解它的涵义
So actually, we know a lot about this already now.
其实我们已经知道很多了
So what does public static mean?
public static 是什么意思呢？
Well, that means we're declaring a static method.
这意味着我们声明了一个静态方法
What about void?
void 呢？
Well, this is a method that returns nothing.
这个方法不返回任何东西
Main-- that's the name of a method.
main 是方法的名称
And here is seemingly some parameter.
这里似乎有一些参数
Well, that seems a little funny.
看起来有点滑稽
And, like, what would-- we're not calling this function from Java,
因为我们不会在 Java 中调用这个函数
so what could this parameter possibly be?
那么这个参数有什么用呢？
Where would-- what is this?
它是什么呢？
Well, hopefully, you've seen command line arguments in the past.
你之前已经见过命令行参数了
And so in Java, when you want to access the command line arguments,
在 Java 中，当你想要访问命令行参数时
you're going to be using this string array.
就要使用这个字符串数组
So here is an example.
这里有一个例子
This class ArgsDemo will print out the 0th command line argument.
ArgsDemo 类将打印出第0个命令行参数
How does it do that?
它是如何实现的？
OK, what does it look like?
它看起来像什么？
Public static void main stream braces args.
public static void main(String[] args)
Well, it just says, System.out.println(args[0]).
它的内容是 System.out.println(args[0])
Prints out the 0th one.
打印出第0个参数
So what would that look like in action?
这在实际中是什么样呢？
Well, if I ran such a program--
我运行一下这个程序
java ArgsDemo hello some args, I expect to get hello.
java ArgsDemo hello some args，期待得到 hello
But let's try it live so we can convince ourselves that this is a real thing. OK?
我们现场尝试一下更有说服力是吧？
ArgsDemo.
ArgsDemo
And all we're going to do is print out the 0th entry of our args array.
我们要打印出 args 数组的第0个元素
And so if we print out-- if we run ArgsDemo, we get error.
如果我们运行 ArgsDemo 会得到错误
Index out of bounds exception.
索引超出边界异常
What's that mean?
那是什么意思？
Oh, well, we didn't give any args.
哦我们还没有提供任何参数
So here is an arg, another arg.
补充 anarg anotherarg
And so n arg, being the 0th one, gets printed first.
因此 anarg 作为第0个参数首先打印出来
Well, why would that be useful?
这有什么用呢？
Well, in the old days, and even now--
在过去，其实现在也有
I mean, if you are a power user of utilities,
假如你使用工具的高级功能
you're aware that there exist programs like, say, FFmpeg or whatever else that you could get at all kinds-- oh, I don't have it on here.
你知道，现在有很多程序，比如 FFmpeg，哦我这里没有
avconv--
avconv...
So there's all these different options you can give it, right?
你可以给它不同的选项
avconv -h.
avconv -h
This is not important.
这些不重要
If you've never used this program, don't worry about it.
没使用过这个程序也不用担心
But basically, this is a command line argument that tells AVcomm what it should be doing.
但基本上这是一个命令行参数，它告诉 avconv 应该做什么
In this case, I just want help.
当前情况下，我只是需要帮助
But if I give it a different sequence of instructions,
但是如果我给它一个不同的指令序列
then it will do other things just so we can use this to give controls to our program--
它就会做其他事情，我们可以通过它来控制我们的程序
hello-- and you will in project 0.
你将在项目0中使用
So let's do a little exercise to make sure we understand what's going on and also the preview of the final topic of the day.
让我们做一些练习确保掌握这些内容，然后预览一下今天最后一个话题
So my goal is I want to now create a program called ArgsSum that will print out sum of the Command line arguments.
我想创建一个名为 ArgsSum 的程序，它将打印出命令行参数的和
And we'll just assume they're numbers.
假设参数都是数字
And what we're going to find that search engines are our friend in this process.
我们会发现搜索引擎是最好的朋友
So I'm going to mimic the process that I would like you to use when you're moving forward learning to program
我模仿一下学习编程的过程，希望你们也是这样
because often, and especially once you're done with courses,
因为通常，尤其是当你学完课程后
you can't just go ask somebody in person, what do I do?
你不能直接去问别人该怎么做？
I mean, sometimes you can, and sometimes, you've just never seen the thing at all.
有的时候可以问，有的时候你一点都不知道
And in fact, that's happened-- that will happen in this class.
这早晚在这门课上发生
There'll be things that I don't explicitly teach that I expect you to go learn--
有一些东西我没有明确讲出来，希望你们自学
nothing so crazy, and I'll cover all the big stuff.
这很正常，我会把重要的讲出来
But a lot of times, there's little details that it's just good to know how to find.
你只需要自己找到剩下的细节就好了
It's good to be independent.
这对独立有帮助
So let's call this program ArgsSum.
我们称这个程序为 ArgsSum
And so what we're going to do now is I'm going to say,
接下来
int N equals Args.length.
int N = args.length
That is the length of our array, and we know that from homework 0.
这是数组的长度，作业0中提到了
Now, I'm going to create another variable called I.
再创建一个变量 i
And then let's say, as long as I is less than N,
只要 i 小于 N
we're going to add to a Sum.
我们就要加和
Sum equals sum plus args I.
sum = sum + args[i]
And then finally, we will print out our sum.
最后打印出总和
So let's try running this.
运行一下
Oops, wrong one. ArgsSum.
弄错了，应该是 ArgsSum
So in this case, we get incompatible types.
在本例中，我们得到了“类型不兼容”错误
String cannot be converted to int.
字符串无法转换为 int
So what do you do now?
应该怎么改呢？
Well, in the old days, you might have to go crack open a reference manual.
在过去，你可能得去翻开一本参考手册
But these days, it's much easier to be lazy and say convert string integer Java.
现在更容易偷懒了，搜索“Java 字符串转整型”
And that's a perfectly fine thing to do in this class.
这样做很好
In fact, it's a really good idea.
思路很不错
So we might look at whatever the top Google link is.
我们看看最上面的链接是什么
But I find that Stack Overflow is often great because it gives examples.
但是我发现 Stack Overflow 很好，因为它提供了示例
So how can I convert a string to an int in Java?
“在 Java 中如何将字符串转换为整型呢？”
My string contains only numbers, and I want to return the number it represents.
“我的字符串只包含数字，我想返回它表示的数字”
Great Stack Overflow question-- ooh, even with an example.
好问题！甚至举了个例子
So the response, since this is such a great question in terms of well-statedness-- someone is able to give an example,
这个问题很好，人们可以用这个例子回答
and we see int fu equals integer parseInt.
我们看到 int foo = Integer.parseInt()
Well, I'm just going to copy that into my code.
把它复制到我的代码中
I guess what I want to do is--
我想我要做的是...
this is the string, so I'll do integer.parseInt and that thing.
这是字符串，所以我要用 Integer.parseInt 处理这个东西
And so I'm hoping this will work.
希望可以奏效
We'll find out.
我们会弄清的
And I'm not 100% certain it will work, but-- oops. Wrong program.
不确定会成功，但是....哎呀程序名错了
OK, it seemed to compile.
它似乎编译成功了
Now, let's test it out.
我们来测试一下
Infinite loop.
无限循环
Ah, I forgot to increment I.
啊我忘了自增 i
And we run it, and we get 10, 15, 25.
运行得到10、15、25
Great. We did it. OK.
太棒了成功了
So we've written a program that will sum the command line arguments, and we used Stack Overflow to get us there.
那么我们编写了一个对命令行参数求和的程序，并且使用 Stack Overflow 解决问题
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
That is a great thing to know how to do.
知道怎么做是一件很棒的事情